var quiz = [

{
	"question" : "SQUAD",
	"correctanswer": "CREW",
	"answer2": "FLASHY",
	"answer3": "SLEEPOVER",
	"answer4": "A GROUP OF SQUID",

},

{

	"question" : "SPILL THE TEA",
	"correctanswer": "TELL ME THE GOSSIP",
	"answer2": "SPILLING HOT TEA",
	"answer3": "LET'S GO",
	"answer4": "I NEED TO PEE",
},

{

	"question" : "SNATCHED",
	"correctanswer": "ON POINT",
	"answer2": "TO TAKE",
	"answer3": "STEEL",
	"answer4": "TIGHT",
},

{

	"question" : "HELLA",
	"correctanswer": "A LOT OF",
	"answer2": "HELLO",
	"answer3": "THE UNDERWORLD",
	"answer4": "TO MUCH",
},

{

	"question" : "GUCCI",
	"correctanswer": "GOOD",
	"answer2": "HEY",
	"answer3": "THE FASHION BRAND",
	"answer4": "GUCCI MANE",
},

{

	"question" : "DANK",
	"correctanswer": "AWESOME",
	"answer2": "A SOUND",
	"answer3": "SOMETHING POSITIVE",
	"answer4": "DUDE",
},

{

	"question" : "WOKE",
	"correctanswer": "BEING AWARE OF THE TRUTH",
	"answer2": "WAKE UP",
	"answer3": "MORNING",
	"answer4": "YES",
},

{

	"question" : "FAKE NEWS",
	"correctanswer": "FABRICATED NEWS STORIES",
	"answer2": "TRUMP",
	"answer3": "YOU STINK",
	"answer4": "SHUTUP",
},

{

	"question" : "HUMBLE BRAG",
	"correctanswer": "SELF PROMOTION",
	"answer2": "STAYING WOKE",
	"answer3": "DOWN TO EARTH",
	"answer4": "NICE",
},

{

	"question" : "#BLESSED",
	"correctanswer": "LUCKY",
	"answer2": "THANK YOU",
	"answer3": "KEEP GOING",
	"answer4": "AGREE",
},

]
